summify.com 2012-06-22

# Privacy Policy - Summify

Last Revised: April 15, 2010

Context Media Technologies, Inc. ("Context") is the company that runs the "Summify" service found at [ http://summify.com](http://summify.com/) (the "Site"). This is the Privacy Policy for the Summify service. You accept it when you accept the complete Terms of Service of the Summify service.

This Privacy Policy may be updated by Context and this Privacy Policy may be supplemented or modified by agreements entered into between you and Context from time to time.

In this Privacy Policy, "personal information" means information about an identifiable individual that is not the person's business contact information or work product information. Any data about usage and service operation that is not associated with a specific personal identity is not personal information. As is true of most websites, Context collects and analyzes non-personal data to evaluate how customers use the Site and the Services. Non-personal data collected by Context may include the pages visited on the Site, unique URLs visited within the Site, browser type and IP address. Most non-personal data is collected via cookies or other analysis technologies. 

### Collection and Use of Personal Information

Context collects personal information from you when you subscribe for services or products, and may from time to time collect additional personal information in the course of providing such products and services. Context uses such personal information as is reasonably required to process your registration for the Site and to provide services and products to you.

Contact information that you provide to Context may be used to contact you in connection with the Site. For example, depending on which privacy preferences you have indicated to Context, we may use your contact information to provide periodic newsletters or to provide notices regarding changes to the Site or regarding new services or products.

This Site may allow you to publish personal information about yourself and others. By publishing your personal information on such pages, you consent to the publication of such personal information. By publishing personal information about another individual, you represent that you have, where required by applicable privacy laws, obtained the consent of such individuals to publish such information.

Context collects demographic and profile data in connection with the Site and uses such data to tailor each visitor's experience at the Site, showing the user content in which Context thinks you might be interested, and displaying the content according to your preferences.

Context may use customer information for additional purposes that may be identified at or before the time that the information is collected.

### Disclosure of Personal Information

**Context may disclose personal information as follows:**

  * to third party service providers and to affiliated entities in order to carry out work on behalf of Context,
  * to law enforcement agencies for the purposes of investigating fraud or other offences,
  * to legal, financial, insurance, and other advisors or in connection with the sale, reorganization, or management of all or part of its business or operations, and
  * as consented to by you from time to time, including to fulfill any other purposes that are identified when the personal information is collected.

Context will not use or disclose personal information for purposes other than those for which it was collected, except with your consent or as required or permitted by law.

### Cookies and IP Addresses

Context may use your IP address to help identify you and your subscription, gather broad demographic information about our users, diagnose problems with Context systems, and administer the Site. The Site uses cookies to deliver content specific to your interests, according to your preferences, and to save your password so that you are not required to re-enter it while you use the Site.

### Links

The Site may contain links to other websites. Context is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. Please ensure you review the privacy policies of the websites that you visit.

### Security

Context protects against the loss, misuse, and alteration of personal information with security measures appropriate to the sensitivity of the information. However, it is possible that any information transmitted via the Internet may be intercepted by unknown third parties.

### Opt-Out

When appropriate, users of the Site are given the opportunity to (i) opt-out of receiving communications from us, (ii) remove their personal information from our records, or (iii) elect to no longer receive services from Context. If you wish to opt-out of receiving further communications, please contact Context's privacy officer (the "Privacy Officer") by email using the contact information provided below.

### Corrections/Contact

You may contact the Privacy Officer to modify or correct any of your personal information that is under Context's control. You may also direct a written complaint regarding compliance with this Privacy Policy to the Privacy Officer.

### Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, Context's privacy practices in connection with this Site, or Context's collection, use, disclosure, or retention of your personal information in connection with this Site, please contact the Privacy Officer as follows:

Context Media Technologies, Inc. Attention: Privacy Officer c/o Shahrooz Nabavi Fasken Martineau DuMoulin LLP 2900 - 550 Burrard St. Vancouver, B.C.V6C 0A3, Canada

Online: Contact Page
